Finding Aid for Jennifer Granholm papers, 1992-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Policy Division
  - General Office Records
    - Fluery, Emily Work Files (Assistant Policy Advisor)
      - Economic Development
        - Urban Core Mayors 2004
        - Urban Marketing 2005
        - Urban Pioneers 2005
        - Urban Policy Course 2003
        - Venture Capital 2003-2005
        - Wage Discrimination 2004
        - Workforce Action Network (WAN) 2005
        - Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification Act (WARN) 2005
        - Workforce Investment Act (WIA) Reauthorization 2005
        - Wine Decision 2005
        - Workforce Innovation in Regional Economic Development (WIRED) 2006
        - Women, Workplace 2006
        - Work Place 2004
        - Workers Compensation 2003-2004, 2 folders
        - Workforce Development 2003-2006
        - Workforce Investment Act 2004
      - End of the Year Remarks 2004
      - General 2003-2006
      - Governor’s Accomplishments
        - 2006
          - Community Development Block Grants (CDBG) Allocation
          - Detroit
          - General
        - Briefing Book
          - Jobs Today 2006
          - General 2006
        - Department of Labor and Economic Growth (DLEG) 2006
        - General 2004-2005
      - History, Arts, and Libraries
        - Cabinet Action Plan (CAP) 2005
        - Preservation 2005
        - General 2003-2005
      - Strategic Action Plan 2004-2005
      - General 2005
    - Garbarino, Gary Work Files
      - General 2005-2006
      - Agriculture 2006
    - Governor’s Letters of Support 2006
    - Government Performance Project (GPP) 2004, 2008
    - Great Ideas, Practices, and Innovations 2005
    - Hardin, Niya Work Files (Policy Advisor)
      - Adequate Yearly Progress (AYP) Spreadsheets 2010
    - Jobs Today 2005-2006
    - Kimberly Brosky Work Files
      - Licensing Proposal 2003-2004
      - General 2005
    - Kohrman, Ben Work Files (Policy Advisor for Transportation and Human Services)
      - Adult Services 2006
      - Detroit 2006-2007
      - Department of Human Services (DHS)
        - Caseload Fact Sheets 2006, 2008
        - Earned Income Tax Credit (ECIC) 2006-2010
        - Preventative Actions 2006
        - Welfare Reform 2006, 2008
        - General 2006
      - General Correspondence 2006, 2008
      - Human Services, General 2006-2007
      - Michigan Department of Transportation (MDOT) 2006-2007
      - Strategic Priorities 2008
    - Lewis Langham Work Files (Deputy Legal Counsel and Policy Adviser) 2006-2007
    - Local Finance 2005
    - Mackinac Conference
      - 2004
      - 2005
    - Margaret Flanagan 2003
    - Metrics and Measures 2004, 2010
    - Mike McDaniel Work Files (Homeland Security Policy Advisor) 2004
    - Miscellaneous
      - 100 Day Report
        - Budget 2003
        - Civil Rights 2003
        - Department of Community Health (DCH) 2003
        - Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ) 2003
        - Department of Information Technology (DIT) 2003
        - Department of Labor and Economic Growth (DLEG) 2003
        - Department of Management and Budget (DMB) 2003
        - Department of Corrections (DOC) 2003
        - Family Independence Agency (FIA) 2003
        - History, Arts, and Libraries (HAL) 2003
        - Department of Agriculture (MDA) 2003
        - Department of Education (MDE) 2003
        - Department of Transportation (MDOT) 2003
        - State Police (MSP) 2003
        - Military and Veterans Affairs (MVA) 2003
        - General 2003, 2010
      - Appendix B Additions 2003
    - Morrison, Connie Work Files (Transportation Policy Advisor)
      - Border Crossings 2003
      - Critical Bridges 2003
      - Land Use 2003
      - Policy Team 2003-2004
      - Reauthorization 2003-2004
      - General 2003-2005
    - Mortgage Foreclosure Legislation Documents 2008
    - Michigan Public Safety Communication System (MPSCS) Tower Updates 2003
    - Federal Role in Detroit River International Crossing (DRIC) (MSF) 2007
    - Pam Paul--Shaheen Work Files (Health and Human Services Policy Advisor) 2003-2004
    - Pat Cannon (State Americans with Disabilities Act Coordinator)
      - Windmills 2004
      - General 2003-2004
    - Pictures (various events)
      - Benton Harbor Cabinet on the Road 2006
      - Flint, Cities of Promise 2006
      - General 2006-2007
      - Hamtramck Pictures 2006
      - Muskegon Heights Cabinet on the Road 2006
      - Pontiac Photos 2006
      - Saginaw Cabinet on the Road 2006
    - PowerPoint Presentations 2008
    - Problems Solved 2004
    - Correspondence (Scanned Files) 2010
    - Securing Michigan’s Future 2005
    - Stine, Donna Work Files (Policy Advisor)
      - Carbon Sequestration 2009
      - Great Lakes 2009-2010
      - Horses 2010
    - Sue Carnell (Education Policy Advisor): Cherry Commission recommendations 2006
    - Tax Restructuring Plan 2005
    - Urban Agenda 2003-2008
    - Yager, Pam Work Files (Policy Advisor) 2006, 2008
    - General 2003-2007
- Executive Division
  The third series, Executive Division, is divided into four subseries: Executive Assistant's Files (Sherry Hicks), Special Advisor for Economic Development Files (Fred Hoffman), Dossiers of Michigan Service Members Lost in Iraq and Afghanistan, and General Office Records. Sherry Hicks served as Granholm's executive assistant and maintained her correspondence and subject files. Hicks arranged the correspondence chronologically into ingoing and outgoing folders and organized Granholm's subject files alphabetically. In the wake of the 2008 financial crisis, Granholm brought in Fred Hoffman to advise her on economic issues. Hoffman's files document his research into various Michigan companies, the 2009 auto bailout, and the current state of the auto industry in Michigan. The General Office Records contain templates for Granholm's standard correspondence. Of particular interest is the Dossiers of Michigan Service Members Lost in Iraq and Afghanistan subseries (compiled by Linda Droste). Droste maintained files on each of the Michigan soldiers killed in action in Iraq and Afghanistan. These files include biographical information, documentation that the state would fly the flag at half mast, and confirmation that a staff member visited each soldier's family to deliver an American flag and offer condolences. Governor Granholm also called each family personally to offer her condolences.
  - Executive Assistant’s Files (Sherry Hicks)
    - Correspondence
      (arranged by month, usually with separate in and out folder)
      - January-December 2003, 20 folders (Box 148)
      - January-August 2004, 13 folders (Box 148)
      - September-December 2004, 6 folders (Box 149)
      - January-July 2005, 12 folders (Box 149)
      - August-December 2005, 7 folders (Box 150)
      - January-August 2006, 10 folders (Box 150)
      - August-December 2006, 7 folders (Box 151)
      - January-May 2007, 7 folders (Box 151)
      - May-December 2007, 8 folders (Box 152)
      - January-October 2008, 15 folders (Box 152)
      - November-December 2008, 3 folders (Box 153)
      - January-December 2009, 18 folders (Box 153)
      - January-February 2010, 3 folders (Box 153)
      - March-December 2010, 16 folders (Box 154)
    - Subject Files
      - 21st Century Community Learning Center Event 2003 (Box 155)
      - Accelerating Michigan’s Alternative Fuel Industry: Briefing to Governor Jennifer M. Granholm 2007 (Box 155)
      - Administrative Rules 2004 (Box 155)
      - Alamo Nursing Home, Inc. 2004 (Box 155)
      - Alix Partners 2003 (Box 155)
      - Alternative Energy
        - General 2006-2008, 2 folders (Box 155)
        - Michigan Green Jobs Report 2009 (Box 155)
        - Energy Alternatives and Efficiency 2007-2009 (Box 155)
        - Great Lakes Restoration 2007-2008 (Box 155)
      - Anti-Bullying Legislation HB 4162 2007 (Box 155)
      - Anti-Dove Hunting Scientific Data and Information 2003-2004 (Box 155)
      - AMBER (America’s Missing: Broadcast Emergency Response) Plan 2003 (Box 155)
      - Attorney General Amicus Briefs 2002-2009 (Box 155)
      - Auditor General 2003 (Box 155)
      - AWAKE (Association Working Against Keweenaw Exploitation) 2003 (Box 155)
      - Banks 2009-2010 (Box 155)
      - Benton Harbor, City of 2003-2010 (scattered) (Box 155)
      - Blue Cross/Blue Shield of Michigan (BCBSM) 2003 (Box 155)
      - Baraga-Houghton-Keweenaw (BHK) Child Development Board 2003 (Box 155)
      - Big Bond Initiative 2005 (Box 155)
      - Blackout (Metro Detroit) 2003 (Box 155)
      - Boilermakers Local 169 2009 (Box 155)
      - Brevet Authorization 2003 (Box 155)
      - Bureau of Workers’ Unemployment Compensation 2003 (Box 155)
      - Business Development Advisors 2007 (Box 155)
      - Cadence Network, Inc. 2003 (Box 155)
      - Center for Innovative Policy Best Practices and Policy Manual 2008 (Box 155)
      - Carter, Maurice (Department of Corrections) 2003 (Box 155)
      - CDBG (Ironwood Plastics) 2003 (Box 155)
      - Charles Kane, President -- One Laptop per Child undated (Box 155)
      - Client Assistant Program 2003 (Box 155)
      - Chronic Wasting Disease Task Force 2003 (Box 155)
      - Cobo Hall Expansion 2008-2009 (Box 155)
      - Collier, Rob, The Public Strategies Group undated (Box 156)
      - Community Colleges, Ten Year History of Fall Enrollments 2003 (Box 156)
      - Community Health, Department of (Medicaid Pharmaceutical Pooling) 2003 (Box 156)
      - Cool Cities
        - General 2004 (Box 156)
        - Pilot Program Top 23 2004, 9 folders (Box 156)
      - Consulates General 2003-2004 (Box 156)
      - Court Cases 2003 (Box 156)
      - Critical Assets -- What Michigan Can Offer the World? undated (Box 156)
      - Detroit Area Regional Transit Authority (DARTA) 2003 (Box 156)
      - Deutsche Energie-Agentur (DENA), 1st German American Energy Conference 2009 (Box 156)
      - DINA Group 2003 (Box 156)
      - DaimlerChrysler Investment in Michigan 2002 (Box 156)
      - Dearborn, City of 2004 (Box 156)
      - Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ) 2003-2005 (Box 156)
      - Deloitte (Project Innovation Quest) 2007 (Box 156)
      - Detroit Electrical Joint Apprentice Training Committee (JATC) Photovoltaic Tour undated (Box 156)
      - Detroit Medical Center 2003, 2008 (Box 156)
      - Detroit Medical Center Updates 2003-2010 (Box 156)
      - Detroit Public Library circa 2003 (Box 156)
      - Detroit Public Schools 2004-2010 (scattered) (Box 157)
      - Detroit Rescue Mission Ministries (DRMM) 2004 (Box 157)
      - Detroit Water and Sewage Department 2003 (Box 157)
      - Detroit-Wayne County Community Mental Services Program 2006-2007 (Box 157)
      - Detroit Wayne County Health Authority 2004 (Box 157)
      - Dow Chemical Company and Petrochemical Industries of Kuwait Co. -- Business Proposal to the State of Michigan 2008 (Box 157)
      - DTE Energy 2003-2004 (Box 157)
      - Economic Alliance for Michigan 2003 (Box 157)
      - Economic Growth and Development 2002 (Box 157)
      - Ecorse, City of 2009 (Box 157)
      - Education
        - Adequate Yearly Progress (AYP) 2003-2004 (Box 157)
        - Charter Schools 2003 (Box 157)
        - Correspondence (Michigan Education) 2003-2004 (Box 157)
        - Education Reform 2004, 2008 (Box 157)
        - Every Child Matters Education Fund 2003 (Box 157)
        - Great Lakes Scholarship Program undated (Box 157)
        - Lauren Resnick Institute for Learning 2003 (Box 157)
        - Michigan High School Athletic Association 2003 (Box 157)
        - Michigan Elementary and Middle School Principals Association (MEMSPA) 2003 (Box 157)
        - Intermediate School Districts Oakland County 2004 (Box 157)
        - Michigan School Aid Act 2004 (Box 157)
        - No Child Left Behind Act 2002-2004, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - Electricity Choice/DTE undated (Box 157)
      - Emerald Ash Borer (EAB) 2002-2003 (Box 157)
      - Executive Agreement with Ohio 2003 (Box 157)
      - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) 2003-2004 (Box 157)
      - Flint, City of 2003-2009 (scattered) (Box 157)
      - Foreclosures and Predatory Lending in Michigan 2007 (Box 157)
      - Genesee County -- Granholm Challenge 2003 (Box 157)
      - Genesis Project: A Catalyst for Change undated (Box 157)
      - Gibbs -- High Speed Amphibian Technology circa 2005, 1 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 157)
      - Governor Granholm First 100 Days 2003 (Box 157)
      - Governor Engler 2002 (Box 157)
      - Governors of Other States and President of the United States 2003 (Box 157)
      - Grand Valley State University Accountability Report 2007 (Box 157)
      - Greater Detroit Area Health Council, Inc. 2003 (Box 157)
      - Greenville/Fed-Mogul Task Force 2004 (Box 157)
      - Habitat for Humanity International 2003-2004, 2007 (Box 158)
      - Dismissal of 2006 Hatch Act Complaint, 2008 (Box 158)
      - Headlee 2003 (Box 158)
      - Health Care Reform
        - Issues/Topics 2005 (Box 158)
        - Recommendations to Reduce the Economic Burden of Providing Employer-Sponsored Health Care Benefits 2005 (Box 158)
        - The Economic Impact of Health Care in Michigan 2004 (Box 158)
        - Michigan State Medical Society 2003, 2005 (Box 158)
      - Henry Ford Museum undated (Box 158)
      - Highland Park, City of 2003-2004, 2008 (Box 158)
      - HK Motors Project undated (Box 158)
      - Honigman, Miller, Schwartz, and Cohn, LLP (East Detroit Riverfront Development Project) 2002 (Box 158)
      - Hurricane Katrina 2005 (Box 158)
      - Ice Mountain 2003 (Box 158)
      - Internet Voting 2004-2008 (scattered) (Box 158)
      - Inkster Public Schools 2004 (Box 158)
      - Insurance Advocate 2008 (Box 158)
      - Insurance Rate Project 2003 (Box 158)
      - Insurance Commission -- State of Michigan
        - General 2003-2004 (Box 158)
        - Credit Scoring 2002 (Box 158)
        - Redlining in Michigan 2003 (Box 158)
      - Iraq 2007 (Box 158)
      - Intellicon 2003 (Box 158)
      - Jobs for America’s Graduates 2002 (Box 158)
      - John Deere -- Wind Energy undated (Box 158)
      - Kelley Cawthorne 2003-2010 (scattered) (Box 158)
      - Kids Count in Michigan
        - 2003 (Box 158)
        - 2009 (Box 158)
      - Kids First 2002 (Box 158)
      - Land Use Leadership Council 2003-2004 (Box 158)
      - Leaders of the Arab American and Chaldean Communities 2003 (Box 158)
      - Legal Division Documents/Executive Directives 2003-2004 (Box 158)
      - Lenawee County Airport 2003 (Box 158)
      - Letters (addressed to D. C. dignitaries, representatives, and senators)
        - Miscellaneous 2003 (Box 158)
        - Corporate Average Fuel Economy CAFÉ Standards 2003 (Box 158)
        - Community Service Block Grants (CSBG) 2003 (Box 158)
        - S1 Medicare Reform Bill 2003 (Box 158)
        - AmeriCorps 2003 (Box 158)
        - Boeing 7E7 and Dreamliner Manufacturing Facility 2003 (Box 158)
        - HR 1582 Universal Service Fairness Act, 2003 (Box 158)
        - Homeland Security Grand Enhancement Act 2003 (Box 158)
        - HR 2854 State Children’s Health Insurance Program, 2003 (Box 158)
        - Medicare and Medicaid Dual Eligibles 2003 (Box 158)
        - Application of Spirit Airlines Form 14 CFR 2003-2004 (Box 158)
        - Michigan Virtual University (MVU) 2003 (Box 158)
        - Letters to Other Governors re: Manufacturing 2003 (Box 158)
        - Medicaid Letter to President Bush 2003 (Box 158)
        - FY 2004 Agriculture Appropriations Bill, 2003 (Box 158)
        - Internet Tax Freedom Act (ITFA) 2003 (Box 158)
        - Watershed Initiative Grant Program 2003 (Box 158)
        - Urban Area Security Initiative (UASI) Grants 2003-2004 (Box 158)
        - 8 Hour Ozone National Ambient Air Quality Standard 2003 (Box 158)
        - Utility -- August 14 Blackout 2003 (Box 158)
        - Temporary Extended Unemployment Compensation (TEUC) 2003 (Box 158)
        - HB 4367 Supplemental Appropriations for 2003, 2004, 2003 (Box 158)
        - Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC) 2004-2005 (Box 158)
        - Detroit Wayne County Health Authority (DWCHA) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Adult Benefits Waiver (ABW) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Michigan Manufacturing Matters Summit 2004 (Box 158)
        - Congressman Rehberg (Alleging Michigan’s Medicaid funding linked to the building of a football stadium) 2004 (Box 158)
        - New Markets Tax Credit (NMTC) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Thank You Letters to Members of the Michigan Congressional Delegation 2003 (Box 158)
        - Multi-State Prescription Drug Purchasing Pool 2003, 2005 (Box 158)
        - Medicaid Funding 2004 (Box 158)
        - Pension Funding Equity Act 2004 (Box 158)
        - Keweenaw Bay Indian Community 2004 (Box 158)
        - Australia-U.S. Free Trade Agreement (AUSFTA) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Early Learning Opportunities Act (ELOA) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Congratulatory Letter to Pete Hoekstra 2004 (Box 158)
        - FSC/ETI Bill (Marketing, Manufacturing, and Sale of Tobacco Products) 2004 (Box 158)
        - State Homeland Security Grant Program (SHSGP) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Global Engine Manufacturing Alliance (GEMA) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Trade Adjustment Assistance (TAA) 2004 (Box 158)
        - Congressional China Currency Action Coalition 301 2004 (Box 159)
        - Voter Access 2004 (Box 159)
        - Michigan’s Youth Challenge Program 2005 (Box 159)
        - Thank You Letters to Members of Michigan State Legislature 2004 (Box 159)
        - Congratulatory Letter to Carlos Gutierrez 2005 (Box 159)
        - Expansion of Gambling in Michigan 2005 (Box 159)
        - Federal Support for Medicaid 2005 (Box 159)
        - Community Series Block Grant (CSBG) 2005 (Box 159)
        - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF) 2005 (Box 159)
        - Ballast Water Management Act 2005 (Box 159)
        - Energy Policy Act 2005 (Box 159)
        - Soo Lock Celebration 2005 (Box 159)
        - Medicaid Smith-Bingaman Amendment 2005 (Box 159)
        - Medicaid Preferred Drug List 2005 (Box 159)
        - Blue Water Bridge Reconstruction Project 2005 (Box 159)
        - House Reconciliation Package 2005 (Box 159)
        - Energy Prices and Profits 2005 (Box 159)
        - DNA Testing -- Hurricanes Katrina and Rita 2005 (Box 159)
        - Thank You Meeting -- Health Care Proposal 2006 (Box 159)
        - Minnesota Vikings to Build New Stadium 2006 (Box 159)
        - Reductions of Army National Guard Soldiers 2006 (Box 159)
        - Western Hemisphere Travel Initiative (WHTI) 2006 (Box 159)
        - Fiscal Emergency Panel Report 2007 (Box 159)
        - MRAP II Vehicle 2007 (Box 159)
        - Thank You Re: Vote for Unemployment Compensation Extension Act of 2009, 2009 (Box 159)
      - Macomb County Charter Commission 2009 (Box 159)
      - Mackinac Bridge 2005 (Box 159)
      - Manufacturing (The Big Three)
        - General 2004-2009 (Box 159)
        - Chrysler 2005-2008 (Box 159)
        - Ford Motor Company 2006-2008 (Box 159)
        - General Motors 2008-2009 (Box 159)
      - Marquette, City of -- Fire Protection Money 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Association of Secondary School Principals (MASSP) 2003 (Box 159)
      - Medicaid 2002-2006 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Agri-Business Association 2004 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Association of Future Farmers of America (FFA) 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Association of Township Supervisor 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Broadband Development Authority 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Department of Natural Resources and Environment (DNRE) 2010 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan (SCORP) 2008 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Center for Innovation and Reinvention (MCIR) 2009 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Department of Transportation (MDOT)-Transit 2006-2010 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Commission on Law Enforcement Standards 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Economic Development Corporation (MDEC) 2005 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Emergency Management Plan (MEMP) 2005-2006, 2 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 159)
        (includes 2 CDs)
      - Michigan Health and Hospital Association 2003-2006, 2 folders (Box 159)
      - Michigan Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Homeland Security 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Homeland Security Building 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Pandemic Influenza Coordinating Committee Annual Report 2007 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Public Service Commission 2003-2007 (scattered) (Box 159)
      - Michigan Land Use Initiative undated (Box 159)
      - Michigan Racing Association 2007 (Box 159)
      - Michigan Venture Capital Association 2008 (Box 159)
      - Michigan State AFL-CIO 2003 (Box 159)
      - Michigan State Board of Education 2003 (Box 159)
      - Military and Veterans 2004 (Box 159)
      - NAACP/MDOT Issues (Correspondence) 2007 (Box 160)
      - National Center for Manufacturing Sciences 2009 (Box 160)
        (includes a USBFlash Drive)
      - NextEnergy 2007 (Box 160)
      - Northern Michigan Hospital 2003 (Box 160)
      - Out of the Box & Over the Barriers: Community-Driven Strategies for Addressing the Uninsured 2002 (Box 160)
      - Oakland County -- Patterson, L. Brooks 2003-2004 (Box 160)
      - Pfizer 2003, 2007, 4 folders (Box 160)
      - Portrait Painters 2004 (Box 160)
      - Pew Charitable Trusts 2008 (Box 160)
      - Pontiac, City of 2009-2010 (Box 160)
      - Project Great Start undated (Box 160)
      - Proton Beam Therapy 2008 (Box 160)
      - Pure Michigan undated (Box 160)
      - Rails to Trails Conservancy 2000 (Box 160)
      - Redevelopment Fast Track Authorities 2003 (Box 160)
      - Representatives from Michigan (Correspondence)
        - Miscellaneous 2003-2004, 4 folders (Box 160)
        - HB 5199 (Prohibits “convicted” child molesters from obtaining release on bond pending sentencing or appeal) 2004 (Box 160)
        - Representative Hardman, Artina Tinsley 2003 (Box 160)
        - Representative Waters, Mary 2003 (Box 160)
        - Representative Birkholz, Patricia 2003 (Box 160)
        - Representative Zelenko, Paula 2003 (Box 160)
      - Ricardo is Fuel Economy 2008 (Box 160)
      - SBC Reforms 2004 (Box 160)
      - School Turnaround 2009 (Box 160)
      - Secretary of State 2003-2004, 2007 (Box 160)
      - Securing Michigan’s Future: The Plan 2002 (Box 160)
      - Senate Bills
        - Senate Bill 117, Sentencing Guidelines for Impersonating a Police Officer 2003 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bill 118, Increased Penalties for Impersonating a Police Officer 2003 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bill 218, Amendments to the Michigan Business Corporation Act 2003 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bill 395, Partial-Birth Abortion 2003 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bill 160, Establishing the Duties and Responsibilities of the State Auditor General 2003 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bill 393, Revised School Code 2003 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bill 1124 Authorizing the State Administrative Board to Convey Certain Parcels of State Owned Property in Various Counties, 2004 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bills 668-672, Changes to State Law Regarding Foster Children 2008 (Box 160)
        - Senate Bill 235, Making, Supplementing, and Adjusting Appropriations for Certain Capital Outlay Programs 2005 (Box 160)
        - Substitutes for House Bills 2004-2005 (Box 160)
      - Senate Resolutions 2003 (Box 160)
      - Senate Rules 2003 (Box 160)
      - Senators (Correspondence) 2003-2010 (Box 161)
      - Single Business Tax -- Reform Negotiations 2005, 2003-2006 (Box 161)
      - Tax Reform 2004 (Box 161)
      - Slovakia 2003 (Box 161)
      - Stallworth, Keith, Wayne County Commissioner 2003 (Box 161)
      - Southeast Michigan Consortium for Water Quality 2003 (Box 161)